const contest_1_3 = [
    {
        "S/N": 1,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "For a first order reaction the half-life is independent of the initial reactant concentration.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 2,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Adding a catalyst to a second order reaction increases the activation energy of the reaction.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 3,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "In an exothermic reaction, the sum of internal energies of the products is lower than that of the reactants.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 4,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The oxidation state of carbon in calcium carbide is -2 .",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False. $\\left[\\right.$ For $\\left.\\mathrm{CaC}_{2}, \\quad \\mathrm{C} \\quad=\\quad-1\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 5,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The oxidation state of carbon in methanal and methanoic acid are the same.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False. $\\left[\\mathrm{H}_{2} \\mathrm{CO}, \\mathrm{C}=0 ; \\mathrm{HCOOH}, \\mathrm{C}=+2\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 6,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The oxidation state of carbon in methanol is lower than that of carbon in methanal.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True. $\\left[\\mathrm{CH}_{3} \\mathrm{OH} \\equiv \\mathrm{CH}_{4} \\mathrm{O} \\quad\\right.$ hence $\\left.\\mathrm{C}=-2 ; \\quad \\mathrm{H}_{2} \\mathrm{CO} \\quad \\mathrm{C}=0\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 7,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A diploid cell has half the number of chromosomes as a haploid cell",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 8,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A diploid cell has four times the number of chromosomes as a haploid cell",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 9,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A diploid cell has two times the number of chromosomes as a haploid cell",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 10,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The apical meristem in the root is located behind the root cap",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 11,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The apical meristem in the root produces cells which become incorporated into the root cap",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 12,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The apical meristem in the root gives rise to the primary meristematic tissues",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 13,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "If $\\log _{a} b=1 / c$, then $b=a^{-c}$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 14,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "$3 \\log x+1=\\log 10 x^{3}$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 15,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "If $\\log _{b} a=c$, then $a=b^{c}$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 16,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The lines with equations $x+2 y=10$ and $2 x+y=5$ are perpendicular",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 17,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The lines with equations $x+y=2$ and $y=5-x$ are parallel.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 18,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The lines with equations $3 x+y=5$ and $x-3 y=5$ are perpendicular.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 19,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A measurement is accurate if it has more significant figures than the true value.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 20,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "An accurate value must be identical to the true value.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 21,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Two measurements of the same quantity can be different from each other and still be accurate.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 22,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The intensity of sound observed at a distance of $1 \\mathrm{~m}$ from a sound source is four times the intensity observed at a distance of $2 \\mathrm{~m}$ from the source.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 23,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A graph of sound intensity from a source against squared distance from the source is a straight line.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 24,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The intensity of sound observed at a distance of $1 \\mathrm{~m}$ from a sound source is half the intensity observed at a distance of $0.5 \\mathrm{~m}$ from the source.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    }
]

export default contest_1_3